{
    "subject": "resource/WGGS-TV",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Spartanburg,_South_Carolina",
    "human_readable": "WGGS-TV is located in Spartanburg, South Carolina.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9721111059188843,
            "question": "Where in South Carolina is WGGS-TV situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8899968266487122,
            "question": "Where is WGGS-TV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8368960022926331,
            "question": "What is the location of WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8336778879165649,
            "question": "What is the broadcast location of WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7702016234397888,
            "question": "What state is WGGS-TV in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7458794713020325,
            "question": "In what city can you find WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.657476544380188,
            "question": "Can you name the state where WGGS-TV broadcasts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6398943662643433,
            "question": "What city is home to WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6392505168914795,
            "question": "To which city does WGGS-TV serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6176859140396118,
            "question": "Is WGGS-TV a television station?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WGGS-TV is located in Spartanburg, South Carolina.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6109_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which city does WGGS-TV serve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6109_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is home to WGGS-TV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6109_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name the state where WGGS-TV broadcasts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6109_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6109_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that WGGS-TV is actually located in Greenville, South Carolina."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the context provided, WGGS-TV is located in Greenville, South Carolina, not Spartanburg. Therefore, the statement that WGGS-TV is located in Spartanburg, South Carolina, is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}